sibcycline.com 2013-06-29

# 

PRIVACY POLICY - COMMITMENT TO YOUR PRIVACY

We at SIBCY CLINE Realtors and Affiliates (referred to as Sibcy Cline) recognize the importance of protecting the privacy of individual-specific information ("Information’) collected about our customers and prospective customers (referred to as "Customers," "you" or "your"). At SIBCY CLINE, it is our intention to give you as much control as possible over your privacy in regard to your Information and the use we make of it in the course of your use of our website(s) located at [www.sibcycline.com](http://www.sibcycline.com/),  [www.sibcy.com](http://www.sibcy.com/), [www.scrsmove.com](http://www.scrsmove.com/), [www.sibcyclinemortgageservices.com](http://www.sibcyclinemortgageservices.com/), [www.sibcyclinerelocation.com](http://www.sibcyclinerelocation.com/), [www.sibcyclineinsurance.com](http://www.sibcyclineinsurance.com/) (referred to as "website" or "our site"). ** ** Our mailing address is **8044 Montgomery Rd, Suite 300, Cincinnati, OH 45236.** We can be reached via e-mail at [customercare@sibcycline.com](mailto:customercare@sibcycline.com) or you can reach us by telephone at 513-985-4010.

Since we gather certain types of information about our users, we feel you should fully understand our policy and the terms and conditions surrounding the capture and use of that information. This privacy statement discloses what information we gather and how we use it, and how to correct or change it.

INFORMATION SIBCY CLINE GATHERS AND TRACKS

SIBCY CLINE gathers information about customers in two ways:

·         Registration: Information that users provide through optional and voluntary submissions. These are voluntary submissions to receive our Home Watch Service, to email a friend, and for scheduling appointments. Customers also provide information on our site to contact an agent to get further information on listings.   

·         Usage tracking: Information SIBCY CLINE gathers through aggregated tracking information derived mainly by tallying page views (using IP address log analyses and through the use of Cookies) throughout our sites. This information allows us to better tailor our content to customers' needs and to help us better understand the demographics of our audience.  Under no circumstances does SIBCY CLINE divulge any information about an individual user to a third party. 

Usage tracking

SIBCY CLINE tracks user traffic patterns throughout all of our sites. However, we do not correlate this information with data about individual users. SIBCY CLINE does break down overall usage statistics according to a user's browser type, and MIME type by reading this information from the browser string (information contained in every user's browser).

SIBCY CLINE sometimes tracks and catalogs the search terms that users enter in our Search function, but this tracking is never associated with individual users. We use tracking information to determine which areas of our sites users like and don't like based on traffic to those areas. We do not track what individual users read, but rather how well each page performs overall. This helps us continue to build a better service for you.

Cookies

We may place a text file called a "cookie" in the browser files of your computer. The cookie itself does not contain Personal Information although it will enable us to relate your use of this site to information that you have specifically and knowingly provided. But the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. SIBCY CLINE uses cookies to track user traffic patterns (as described above). 

You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. If you've set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies, you will receive the warning message with each cookie. You do not need to have cookies turned on to use this site. However, you do need cookies to participate actively in message boards, forums, polling, surveys, user session customization and membership services. Some of the features of the site may have limited or missing, or broken functionality if you choose not to accept cookies. 

"E-mail this to a friend" policy

Our site users can choose to electronically forward a link, page, or documents to someone else by clicking "e-mail this to a friend". The user must provide their email address, as well as that of the recipient. This information is used only in the case of transmission errors and, of course, to let the recipient know who sent the email. The information is not used for any other purpose.

**_Privacy Policy Use_** ****

_How the information you gather is used if relevant?_

USE OF INFORMATION

SIBCY CLINE uses any information voluntarily given by our users to enhance their experience in our network of sites, whether to provide interactive or personalized elements on the sites or to better prepare future content based on the interests of our users.

As stated above, we use information that users voluntarily provide in order to send out Home Watch Alerts and to help our customers with the home buying and selling process.

We use tracking information to determine which areas of our sites users like and don't like based on traffic to those areas. We do not track what individual users read, but rather how well each page performs overall. This helps us continue to build a better service for you. We track search terms entered in Search function as one of many measures of what interests our users. But we don't track which terms a particular user enters.

SIBCY CLINE creates aggregate reports on user demographics and traffic patterns for Sibcy Cline and its affiliate companies.  We will not disclose any information about any individual user except to comply with applicable law or valid legal process or to protect the personal safety of our users or the public.

SHARING OF THE INFORMATION

As a general rule, SIBCY CLINE REALTORS will not disclose any of your personal Information except when we have your permission or under special circumstances, such as when we believe in good faith that the law requires it or under the circumstances described below. The following describes some of the ways that your Information may be disclosed.

_SIBCY CLINE REALTORS Real Estate Brokers_ : SIBCY CLINE REALTORS may disclose information about you to SIBCY CLINE’s brokers and Realtors who would like to contact you for general marketing purposes.

_Business Partners & Sponsors_: SIBCY CLINE REALTORS may disclose some or all your Information to business partners or sponsors, but this use will be specifically described to you prior to data collection or prior to transferring the data. Many promotions offer opportunities to request additional Information from sponsors. By requesting more information, you give SIBCY CLINE REALTORS permission to transfer your information to the sponsor so they can fulfill your request. In many instances, only your e-mail address will be shared. If more Information will be shared with the sponsor, you will be notified prior to the transfer.

_Third Party Data and Data in the Aggregate_ : From time to time, you may be offered the opportunity to receive materials or special offers from third parties. If you opt to receive information from these third parties, SIBCY CLINE REALTORS will **** (with your permission) share your name and email address with such third parties. Under confidentiality agreements, SIBCY CLINE REALTORS may match Customer Information with third party data. Also, SIBCY CLINE REALTORS discloses aggregated Customer statistics (for example, 50% of our Customers are male) in order to describe our services to prospective partners, advertisers, and other third parties, and for other lawful purposes.

SIBCY CLINE uses the above-described information to tailor our content to suit your needs and help us better understand our audience's demographics. We will not share information about individual users with any third party, except to comply with applicable law or valid legal process or to protect the personal safety of our users or the public.

From time to time, for customers who visited our site, we make the customer information available to other Sibcy Cline business partners and affiliates whose products or services we think you might find interesting. If you supply us with your mailing address you will only receive the information for which you provided us your address. Customers who supply us with their telephone numbers may receive a telephone call from us with information regarding new products and services or upcoming events. 

We may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically.

SECURITY

SIBCY CLINE operates secure data networks protected by industry standard firewall and password protection systems. Our security and privacy policies are periodically reviewed and enhanced as necessary and only authorized individuals have access to the information provided by our customers.

OPT-OUT POLICY

We give users options wherever necessary and practical. Such choices include:

·         **Opting not to register to receive our Home watch Subscription.  
  
**

·         **Opting not to participate in certain interactive areas, which completely alleviates the need to gather any personally identifiable information from our users**

You should contact customercare@sibcycline.com for any opt out requests.

YOUR CONSENT

By using this site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by SIBCY CLINE. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.
